Dear Gas, I am washing my face.  Tell me I am
washing my face.  I feel something strange in my eyes.
A random aunty's voice is coming.
She is saying don't rub, don't rub.  Just
add water.  Don't rub.  I am Doctor.   Do
n't rub.  Now my mind is blinded
but still I am thinking that this is the doctor who leaked the paper.   I had a
great week
last week.  I did not even book a return ticket,
sir.  I had reached Jantar Mantar on the 20th itself.
You people have got the vibe here, you got the
vibe from Instagram, it is going on there,
you people have to say Inquilab Zindabad,
okay, will you
just keep running the reel,
okay, Inquilab Zindabad,
this is going on, Inquilab
Zindabad,
suddenly someone tapped it brother,
I said yes, will you eat Burger King, I have been doing it for a
long time, this was not there from the first day,
all this started from the second day, the
scene of the first day was very different.  Me and my
flat in the cold.  We both got bored.
We have to go to Jantar Mantar protest.  Let's
go to Parliament 20th July 9 am Let's go to Parliament.  This is what
we have been told.  We reached there sir,
we reached there happily cutting the meat.
Whose beautiful building did we see outside the Jantar Mantar site?
Then we did not get any hint from LIC that they were
giving last chance.   If you want to
take it, take insurance now.  We
thought wow, what a beautiful building.  Our
first protest is na we were nubs.
Brother, we went there and there were these type of young
people, ma'am, I saw a boy,
his face was so smooth, sir, neither do you have a beard nor do
I have a beard.  You grow a moustache.  His
face doesn't know what a moustache is.  Do you
understand?  Mowgli Mowgli salvation.   Do you
understand what I am saying?
Looking at him, it seemed as if if you
ask him to recite the 12th table, he will recite it.
He is coming and he can see it.  He is
standing with that black art which people have written and kept, in which it is
written that education is a
category of milk.  The more one drinks, the more he will
roar.  He is standing holding Ambedkar ji's coat.
But if you see it once, you will
understand.  This is the only one who needs milk.
That boy is standing there.  My
flatmate and I talked to him.  I said,
brother, with whom have you come?  He says I have come alone.
He said why?  He is saying that my sister and
brother have been attempting NEET exam for the last 3 years.
People have been doing something or the other for the last 3 years.
My father drives an auto rickshaw.
He got coaching in the first year.  After that, when the
money ran out, he got it done digitally.
This year she was preparing on her own.
Leaked it this time also.  That's why I have come.
why did you come?  asking Bundy.  Bundi is saying,
brother, I think
Rancho is not on hunger strike.
This is an AI generated video.  This is fake.  I have come to
confirm.  Hey, you tell me,
Rancho Hunga is on strike since June 28.
So who got married for the third time on July 5
?
He is telling this to an 11th class boy.  Hey, that's
Aamir Khan.  Both are different.   He is
asking me why have you come?  I
said, friend, what I meant to say was that I am not
anti-BJP.  Neither am I a pro
CJP nor do I have anything.  I
am anti-silence.  The poor guy is sitting there hungry.
Now this is not a political issue.  There is a moral
issue right now.  No one is answering.
You also got the paper leaked.  I have come here for that cause.
I said your parents know
you are here.  He doesn't say anything.  Do your
parents know?  I said no.  I
said yes, now we will roam around together.
Then all three of us spent the entire protest together.  There was
so much crowd brother.  I
went to such a place for the first time.  This does not mean that it
is indoors somewhere.  This is outdoor.  The sky is visible.
You still feel suffocated.   There
is so much crowd there.  One after another people have
come.  Slogans are being raised, sir.
Dharmendra Pradhan should resign.  Dharmendra
Pradhan should
resign.
Show unity guys.
This is because you people are sitting broken, that is why the
government comes to power.
Unity is revealed only in the movement.  Do you understand
sir?  Showing strength is.  We have to
speak unitedly.  Long live Mother India.
Tamil Pradhan
two.
Now you tell me one thing.   There is
so much crowd gathered there.
They have blocked the internet in a radius of two to three kilometres.
This is a protest against Instagram.
People are busy there.  Dharmendra Pradhan should
resign.
Dharmendra Pradhan should
resign.   Even
if he had given it that day, the crowd would have been doing the same.
Because the internet is not working.   The
same thing would have happened even if Modi ji had resigned.
People were not prepared there.  Neither
the police was prepared nor were any of the cockroach Janata Party
people prepared.  People have just reached there.  are
engaged.  And I will not even
call them protesters.   Isn't it
?  They were intellectuals.
They were intellectual people.  Isn't it?  The net is not
working.  Still, we are gathering people there from our side.
A girl who had
come from another city just like us.   She has
come there after taking leave from her job.  She is standing outside and
smoking a cigarette.  An aunty
comes to him and is talking.  You have come here to do all this.
Generation war has happened now.  Parents
vs Kids has been held at the national level at Jantar Mantar.
Parents are saying no, no, we should not
go there.  Dadu ji has forbidden it.  Yes, the
children are saying that it is our
mistake.  She has come there to do all this, you have come
here.  She is saying, Aunty, I don't
even smoke cigarettes.  I am blowing this in protest.
There he is sitting with an empty stomach.  Rancho is
torturing his body.  I am
harming my body by inhaling smoke.   It is
so wrong, it is unhealthy to
smoke cigarettes, still the government allows it, that is why
people buy it, if the government does not allow it then no
one will buy it, it is the
government's fault, aunty is saying,
yes it is the government's fault, she said come
aunty, you also come, she took me inside, there were so many
smart intellectual people,
brother this is going on, people are having fun there,
slowly I understood that here no
one knows what to do here, the
internet is down.  People are just there.   They are shouting
slogans.  Include Modi also in Go Pradhan Go Pradhan Go.
Go Pradhan Go
was so catchy.  I mean,
how do I make this a ringtone?  Very hey that vibe was different.
That is why I am asking you to repeat that
brother, you should feel a little protest like this, 5%, 10%.
Whatever I do there will be fun.
You guys keep having fun.  There is some
colourful protest programme every two months.  It's fun.
They saw that this crowd was not moving.
They have understood that they will have to be driven away.
These people are sitting with great anger.
They slowly started throwing tear
gas.  There is a little wine type calculation of tear gas,
ma'am.  Its aquire test.   It
bursts there the first time.  Tear gas
will come.  Your eyes are burning so much.   There will be
tears obviously.  It feels like
my nose hair has burned?  Yes, I do
n't know what is happening,
some chemical is stuck deep inside the throat, here also you are
swallowing spit, I don't know the spit is going inside
but this chemical is not going inside, why am I
not able to swallow it, Nitin Gadkari is stuck here,
what is this stuck, you will burst, you are
not able to understand, you are irritated and
your water is finished, you are
standing there for a long time, you have come from far away, I
reached there early in the morning in Delhi, your
water is finished, but every time
gas is being thrown from there, some random
stranger is giving you water from his bottle
every time.  It never happened even once that
tear gas came and there was no water at hand.  Someone
or the other is less like his bottle.  Is giving.
But it did explode with a little of our
tear gas.  Isn't it?  I told the prisoner, let's go brother.
We have slowly finished
our protest today.  Isn't it?  I will
leave slowly.  That 11th class boy, his name is
Raghav.  He heard us talking about leaving.  He is
saying, did you guys come here because you were
bored?  Are?  Is that why you came?  I go home
daily because he also has a sting in his eye.  Is
that why you came?  Meaning brother, it
's okay brother, I have grown the entire moustache today.
We are standing.  Then all the random
strangers holding their hands because they can't see.  They are
going forward again and again because
what is their strategy?  The
crowd has to be driven away from the protest side.  They are throwing tear gas.
As soon as the crowd goes away, we will
put up barricades.  Then they will throw tear gas and keep
driving away the barracks.  All the shops in CP
which were open suddenly have to close their shutters.
Customers are sitting inside.  These people are
adopting this strategy.  So the crowd that was
following you, then some people would say
no, go ahead, come forward, come back forward.
So you used to wash your face and everyone is coming forward.   If
someone does not have water, then you have
kept a handkerchief wet so that if tear gas comes, you can
apply it on your eyes.  It gives relief.
I am telling you for next time.   One should
go with a handkerchief.
What a strange situation that was.  Do you understand?
You are trusting a crowd of strangers.
You are afraid of familiar people who are in uniform.  Very strange.  But
look, you people understand whose protest is this?
This protest is of
people between the age of 15 to 25.   At
this age, people have to go to school or college and have
fun.  They are forced to
come to the protest and have fun.
Tear gas occurred two-three times.  After that the boys
adopted him.  They are evolving
slowly.  Clear gas is coming.
After that she came once or twice.  Then they are saying
send the next double apple flavored one.
Send it.  Their fun has begun.  Isn't it?
A boy saw that tear gas was coming from there.
She comes in such a projectile motion.   If
he sees it, it is going to fall behind him.   He
will ask his friend to make a video.   Came down.
He slowly put on his glasses.  As soon as the
gas burst, he is walking in slow motion.
Hey brother, who are these people?  What kind of people are these?
How will you win over them?
Tear gas I am washing my mouth.  You know I'm
washing my face.  I feel something strange in my eyes.
A random aunty's voice is coming.
She is saying don't rub, don't rub.  Just
add water.  Don't rub.  I am Doctor.   Do
n't rub.  Now I have my eyes closed in my mind.
But still I am thinking that this is the doctor who leaked the paper.
Wali is a doctor.
But I trusted him.  Any advice is
good advice at this point.
People were still not stopping.  And
brother, I have to guess the tears.  Ma'am, I later found out it was
expired.
When it enters the nose, then it is not clear that it is
expired.  Then it bursts brother.  Tear gas
also has benefits.  I came to know about this the next day.
You will go home when it is there because there are
chemicals on your face.  The skin also gets a little dry quickly.  When
you wash your face, it feels like you got a
facial.  When you sleep, you
sleep so well that day.  I sleep very well.  I
woke up in the morning and found out I had a
stye in both my eyes.  Anjani says that
swelling occurs near the eyelashes.  I had it
in both my eyes.  I woke up in the morning and it was fine.
Magical, when you
wake up in the morning, you know your vision becomes so clear.
You can see far away.
Whom to vote for next time?
Clarity?  You get clarity brother.
But they have realised that this boy is a fool.   Have
adopted it.  These people are not even moving.  Isn't it
?  The shops are closed but still they are
standing there.  People were standing.  Was
standing there in the crowd.  Not moving.  They
started and then the police chased them.
You came to know later that lathi charge was going on.
When the police was chasing you, you did
not know what he had in his hand.  Then I do
n't understand what
these people are charging.  Are?  You are running in a hurry.
Due to two or three different fears, fear has arisen in your chest.  There
is so much crowd before the police are running.  Don't let this
crush you.  You are running for that.   The
police are chasing him away.  He should have a gun in his hand.
Who knows what might happen.  are you running.  I do
n't understand what is happening.  Raghav
is beside me.  He is saying, brother, I had read in the book that
we became independent in 1947.
Why are you guys running away?  I said brother, at
that time we had become independent from the British.
Still slaves of the leaders.   At that
time we were imprisoned in slavery.   Right now they have
imprisoned us in our freedom.
We are not able to find out.  Isn't it?
This is a different type of game.  King Minister
Protester Police.  He is driving us away.   It was
clear there at that time, right?  The time of the literati was
clear.  On the basis of skin, people were saying that it is
white, good.  Beat the brown munda.
Beat the brown head.  Beat up the brown
heads.  Someone will look brown shaved.   Keep pounding.
What's the problem right now?  It is not the
fault of the policemen.  Now all are brown
shaved.  Everyone has to be beaten.
We hid ourselves.  Did you get beaten or not?  People
asked me whether I was beaten with a stick or not?  We, the
police, moved ahead.  We were CPs
in the market.  We hid somewhere behind the car park.
As those people were chased away.  Then the crowd
dispersed.  You guys know tear gas is
coming.  Still the morale of the people did not
break.  Tear gas is coming there.  Still
people are raising their slogans.  Inquilab
Zindabad.
Inquilab
And then saving tear gas.
Not everyone even has water.
We made our mouth like this.  I am doing it by moving my mouth like this.
Whenever the oppressor commits oppression
from the corridors of power.  Every inch of the place will echo with the
slogans of revolution.  This is what I am doing brother.
What cool people I found them to be.  Are?
Whenever the oppressor commits oppression from the corridors of power.   Every inch of the place will resonate with the
slogans of
revolution, every inch of the place will resonate with the slogans of revolution,
tell me friend, have fun, are you listening, should I use the
stick, then every inch of the place will
resonate,
what did you say with your saliva, someone has
said with your saliva, now what is laro
brother, then you should look at them and
show me that this is
not a crowd gathered by paying money.  This is not a BJP or Congress
crowd.  There are troubled trust people
who have come here for their calls that brother
we are troubled.  Everyone had their own protest.
Everyone's skull is filled with different things.
Some for NEET, some for SSC, some for
CBSE, everyone is standing here and
protesting.  All this is going on there.  I am
not afraid of the stick, ma'am.
I got beaten a lot in my childhood.   Even
in my childhood, the thought used to come to my mind
that oh God, is
my life in danger in this house?
I have been beaten so much.  I was
not afraid of the police, brother.  I was
scared to see what was going on.  This is happening for the first time.  But
this was on the first day.  When this news
reached others, it reached the world.  From the next day onwards
everyone started sympathizing with him.  And students have
come there in large numbers.
People from other cities are delivering food there.  Isn't it
?  When I went there the next day, Sir became more
motivated.  He would not have given water.
Maybe I would have come home the next day.
That water debt fell on me.  Now it was not
about me or about both of us,
a unity had come.  Isn't it?  For the first time, it
feels like we live among ourselves,
that my flatmate, my brother, my
parents, my sister, my children, at that time, he became
ours, that brother, he is my country, this type
of light feeling came.  For the first time
in my life I told myself, brother, now I will have to
stand here.  We stood till the end until we
drove them away.
But the next day the atmosphere there has changed.  The
college fest had already taken place there.   The
boys have adopted it.  I am going there.  I can
see Spiderman.
I said this is brand new.
Came later.  How did this come about now?  Two Spidermen are
visible.  Taking different posters.  Bole
Multiverse.
Hey, what is happening?  Two Gandhijis are visible.
They also have a multiverse, a thin, a fat
girl, looking like a school girl, she goes and
talks to Gandhiji, she talks very seriously,
why is she so seriously, she
asks him, Gandhiji did wrong, didn't he,
yesterday he lathi charged us, he did wrong, we should
also do something, he said no daughter, whatever happens,
we should not take up arms in our hands,
we should not take up arms, the
police chased him from behind, this is the
first time I have heard from Gandhiji's mouth,
daughter, the
best is going on, the woofer guys have come there, the
audio system with boobs, have you heard that song, you have
heard that tamilnadi bas song, it is
playing in Modiji's voice,
why is it, and what is Modiji saying, did
you see the reel he has put up, he
abused me, he spoke inappropriately about my mother,
tell me ma'am, if someone breaks your head with a lathi and it
bleeds, what will you say, oh, scoundrel,
how mischievous is this
naughty, yes, you will say this, he has broken the heads of 18 year old
children, what will you say,
friend, he can do this much at least, but
everyone did not like this Modi
Some people got angry at the voice of Mr. Ji, then
I changed the slogans there to Dharmendra Pradhan
Pradhan
Pradhan,
but when this satsang was going on in the evening,
in the voice of Modi Ji, Dharmendra Pradhan, give me the
speaker, make
your demand clear, do you want to
play music,
and the people were very self-aware, brother,
they did proper garbage, I am seeing that the
young people are also picking up garbage
in black colored polythene bags wearing proper gloves on their hands.  They are
also taking care of others.
Someone is fanning me.  The
fan is rotating like this.  Random fan guy on me too.
Hey, I'm a VIP.  Someone is offering Burger King.
Someone is running a fan.  Nice brother, I enjoyed it.
I met Raghav on the first day.
We did not talk after that.  That was
our conversation for just one day.  All this started becoming visible from the second day.  Isn't it
?  The college
fest has slowly started there.  But after that
I never went to Delhi.  I used to go there to
check whether the arrangements were right or
not. I used to go there with the responsibility
that there is no shortage of crowd or not.
I used to motivate people by saying that come,
everything is available there, there is food here, there is khichdi, there are potatoes, there is
medical aid,
some people are sitting there with sanitary pads but the boys are not motivated, it is
full of fun inside, I said
ganja is also available, come, come. People used to
come there with me in the crowd, I used to
hide somewhere in the crowd and go out, somewhere brother, will you
keep sugar, an ant has come, remove the sugar, the ant is there, bring
them there and stop them.
Everyone is implementing their own strategies.  And you know the auto
drivers have helped a lot.  Auto drivers are
telling me a lot that whenever I am going home by
auto, they told me that I have
dropped many girls like this.  I used to
take it from Jantar Mantar because they
closed the washroom.  Zomato was also shut down
after the first or second day.  So I used to take it and
feed them.  He used to take me to the washroom and then
drop me back and I did not take even a single rupee.
And you tell them that I
am a student, so I was dropping you to Jantar Mantar for free.  No matter
how much you do.  A new slogan
started there.  Modi, your dictatorship will not work, it will not
work, we will do it with force, okay Modi,
your dictatorship will
not work, it will not work,
Modi, your dictatorship will not work, it will not work, there is
power, brothers, people said together, he has some
power, I did not understand, then when
finally the resignation came,
yes, that day there was such a different atmosphere there,
people were so happy, I saw, when I went back there to
visit, everyone was cleaning, there was an
atmosphere of happiness, people did not lose courage,
there also a play card was kept, season
two Nitin Gadkari season three
Nirmala Tai season in filming,
Narendra Modi, hey brother, what fun is going on
there, these protests, I
told him, brother, I started liking Delhi, it started looking like a very
politically and historically relevant place,
I fell in love with Delhi,
brother, on the day of resignation, we were going back
home in an auto, then a brother very
nicely told me a couple of good things, he said,
brother, resignation was bound to happen, you are saying to yourself that
Ravana will never win in this country.
Ram will always win.  No matter how
dark the darkness is, it can never
consume the sun.  He said, why are you feeling so much
?  What happened to you?  He said,
no brother, my daughter is also attempting NEET for the last three years.  In the
first year, I
somehow managed to arrange money for his coaching.  The
second year I got it done online.
Now they have leaked this paper again.
I said, will you now get his daughter
married?  Now you will feel some pressure.  He
said, no no, I will teach him as long as he wants to
study, brother, I am also a Brahmin.
We have also voted a lot for the government.
But now we have understood.  This has not been done properly.
What is happening is not wrong.
He has also killed children.  Not right.  I am
your only daughter.  He said, no no, I
also have a son who is in 11th.  He
comes first in the class and is smart.  I said, is his
name Raghav?  He said, yes, did you
meet him in the protest?   He
said, no no, another friend of mine
named Raghav,
he might have gone, brother, he might have gone to the protest,
his mother had forbidden
him a lot, but he must have gone after his father,
he was very different, his wife was very different,
sir, there was hope, suddenly the auto drivers are saying
that they have stolen the votes, they have
also stolen the money from the temple, now what is it, so
this protest, that brother, we
can raise our voice, this was their hope and
for me it was also fun, I mean, you guys will probably
watch Spiderman Brand New Day now.   There was nothing better than that,
brother.
I have seen Spiderman.  I don't know why Spiderman is standing holding it
in his hand.  My
pad leaks less than neat papers.
Meaning there's a pretty awesome multiverse.
These people are very clever.  I had a lot of fun,
brother.  I am waiting for the next
protest to happen.
I have only one eye left.
Inquilab Zindabad
Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad
Inquilab Zindabad It is government, it is
government, it is
government, the government is useless, it is government, the government is useless, it is government, Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad
Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad
Inquilab Zindabad It is government, the government is government, the government is government, the government is government, the government is government, the government is government, the government is government, Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Inquilab Zindabad Take Pradhan,
Modi as well, take Pradhan along with Modi, take Pradhan
along with Modi, take Pradhan along with Modi,
take Pradhan along with Modi, well
what did you get here, you got biscuits
and resignation too,
oh hi hi5,
say this Modi, you go